Guide to the Amos Poe Papers, 1966-2005 MSS.203
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Production Files
  - Series II, Subseries B: Financial
    - "Above the Line" [Cost Report], October 20 [no year] (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - "Agent Breaker" [Budgetary, Cost Reports], 1991 - 1992 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - "Agent Breaker" [St. Lucia Budget], 1991 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - "Berlin" [Picture Budget Detail], 1982 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - "Crossbreed" [Cash Flow], 2001 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - "Dead Weekend" [Budget], 1992 - 1993 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - "The Domestication of the Vampire" [Production Estimates with Screenplay Notation], undated (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - "Eden Farm" [Budget Proposal], 1991 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Budget Adjustment II], June 20, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Budget Pass #2], February 13, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Financial Report], May 8, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Music Clearance Budget, Etc.], c1997 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - "The Guitar" [Budget], January 31, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - "The Guitar" [Budget Reports], 1997 - 2000 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - "The Guitar" [Cost Reports], 1996 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - "Hard On Berlin" [Budget], 1991 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - "THe Hole" [Estimates], undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - "Kid Killer" [Budget], 1993 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - "Kid Killer" [Financing Options, Development], 1992 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - "La Pacifica" [Royalties], 1997 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - "Lodz Seven" [1st Draft Budget], 1993 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" [Budget], 1991 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Poe Productions: "Cable Bldg. Bankruptcy", 1994 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Poe Productions: Manhattan Mini Storage, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - "Port of Call" [Unified Field Pictures], August 8, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - "Pronto!" [Scene Reports, Budget], 2005 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" [Budgetary], 1987 - 1988 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - "Sandra Bernhart Live At the Trocadero" [Budgetary], 2002 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - "Save Our City" [Budgetary], February 1992 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Steve Earle [Invoices], 2000 - 2001 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Steve Earle: "Some Other Plans", 2002 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - "Subway Riders" [Budgetary, Treatment Inserts], 1978 - 1981 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - "Tast of the West" [Budget, German], 1985 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - "The Theresa Stern Story" [Budget Recap], 1988 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - "Unmade Beds" [Budget Grids], undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - [Various Projects: Financial File], 1979 - 1980 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Series II, Subseries C: Distribution and Promotion
    - "Agent Breaker" [Press Clips], 1991, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - "Alphabet City" [Atlantic Releasing Corp.], 1984 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - "Alphabet City" [Various], 1983 - 1991 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - "Amos Poe Visions" [Flyer / Mailer], undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - "Amos Poe's Greatest Hits" [Promotional], c1989 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - "The Blank Generation" [BBC Agreement], 1992, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - "The Blank Generation" [Cinema Jove], 1998 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - "The Blank Generation" [Copyright, Print Records], c1991 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - "The Blank Generation" [Distribution, Screening], 1977 - 2003 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - "The Blank Generation" [Distribution, BBC and MTV], 2001 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - "The Blank Generation" [Distribution], 2004 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - "The Blank Generation" [Distribution], 2005 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - "The Blank Generation" [Flyers], various (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - "The Blank Generation" [Folkets Bio Licensing], 1993 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - "The Blank Generation, " "The Foreigner," and "Unmade Beds" [German TV Rights], 1991 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - "The Blank Generation," "Night Lunch" [Global Imageworks Agreements], February 10, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - "The Blank Generation" [Guido Chiesa, Italy], 1993 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - "The Blank Generation" [Music Video Distributors], 2001 - 2005 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - "The Blank Generation" [Press Kit Materials], 1978, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - "The Blank Generation" [Transformer, Inc., Japan], 2005 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - "The Blank Generation" [VH1, MTV, Etc.], 1999 - 2003 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - "The Blank Generation" [VPRO], 1992 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - "The Blank Generation" [Wall to Wall Television, Ltd.], 1991 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - "The Blank Generation," "Subway Riders" [Zweites Deutsches Fernsehen, Germany] (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - "Dead Weekend" [Press], 1995 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Film Tech [Various Productions] (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - "The Foreigner" [New American Filmmakers Series, Whitney Museum of American Art], 1978 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - "The Foreigner," "Subway Riders" [No Wave Cinema, Whitney Museum of American Art], 1996 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - "The Foreigner" [Monday/Wednesday/Friday Video Club], 1990 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - "The Foreigner" [Press Pack Materials], various (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - "The Foreigner," "Unmade Beds" [Screenings], various (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Fortissimo Film Sales, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Freunde der Deutschen Kinemathek [Germany], various (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Distribution], 1997 - 1998 (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Flyers], undated (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Theatrical Release, Screenings], c1999 (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Unstaged Reading, Fifth Night / Nuyorican Poets Cafe], 1996 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - "Hard On Berlin" [World FIlm Services, Inc.], 1993 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - John F. Kennedy Center For the Performing Arts Project, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - "Kid Killer" [Media Kit], c1993 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - "La Pacifica" [Press Release Material], 1994 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - [Matchbooks, Various Titles], undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Millennium Film Workshop Program Calendar, Fall 2004 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - "Mrs. Dogg" [Agreements], 1991 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Music Video Distributors, Inc. [Contracts, Etc.], 2001 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Music Video Distributors, Inc. [Various], 2001 - 2003 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - New Line Cinema [Various], 1982 - 1983 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - [New York Flyers, Various Titles], undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - "Night Lunch" [Promotional], 1977 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Rain Film: DVD Manufacturing, c2001 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" [Agreement], July 16, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Steve Earle: Press Pack Materials, c2002 - 2003 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Sub-Distributors Contact List, undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - "Subway Riders" [Assorted Press + Promotional], 1978 -1983 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - "Subway Riders" [International Press], 1982 - 1983 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - "Subway Riders" [Screening Agreements, Invoices], 1982 - 1983 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - "Subway Riders" [Untitled Text by Glenn O'Brien, Shot Sheets, undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Distribution], 1991 - 1992 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Distribution Expenses], c1991 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - "Triple Bogey" [The Film Society of Lincoln Center], 1992 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - "Triple Bogey" [HBO Agreement], April 16, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Japan Deal], 1993 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - "Triple Bogey" [London Press], 1993 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Netherlands Film Museum], 1993 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - "Triple Bogey" ["Passed Distribution"], 1991 - 1992 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Press Clips], 1991 - 1992 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Production Proposal Materials], c1991 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - "29 Palms" [Screening Questionnaires], 2001 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - "Two Films by Amos Poe" [The Secret Cinema, Moore College of Art and Design], undated (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - "Unmade Beds" [Promotional], undated (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - "Unmade Beds" [Valhalla Films, Australia], 1982 - 1988 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - "Unmade Beds," "Blank Generation" [Invoices, Promotional], c1977 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - [Various: Commerical Invoices], 1998 - 2004 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - "Xodus 5" [Press Pack Materials], c2000 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Series II, Subseries D: Film Festivals
    - "Agent Breaker," "Triple Bogey" [Festival Internazionale del Film, Locarno], 1991 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - "The Blank Generation," "Unmade Beds" [The Deauville Festival, France], 1977 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - "The Blank Generation," "Dead Weekend," "Triple Bogey" [Olympia Film Festival], 1995 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - "The Blank Generation" [Viennale Internationale Filmfestwochen Wien, Austria], 1995 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Color Sync 2000 Showcase [Cantor Film Center Program], February 3, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - "Dead Weekend" [Stockholm International Film Festival], 1995 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Festival dei Popoli [Italy], 1993 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Festival Internazionale Cinema Giovani, Torino [Italy], 1982 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Festival Internazionale Cinema Giovani, Torino [Italy, Press Book], 1982 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Festival Internazionale Cinema Giovani, Torino [Italy], October 1984 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Festiwalowe [Poland], 1993 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - [Film Festival Badges: Various], 1991 - 1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - [Film Festival Expenses], c1991 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - [Film Festivals - "Passed"], 1991 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Film Foundation North Rhine-Westphalia, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - First Run Film Festival [New York University], 1999 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - First Run Film Festival [New York University], 2001 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - First Run Film Festival [New York University], April 2002 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - First Run Film Festival [New York University], April 2003 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - "The Foreigner" [Edinburgh International Film Festival], 1978 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - "The Foreigner" [Festival Internacional de Cine Gijon, Spain], 2004 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Nantucket Film Festival], 1998 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Noir in Festival, Italy], 1998 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - "Frogs For Snakes" [Popcorn Film Festival, Sweden], 1998 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Immediate Film Festival [New York University], 2004 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - International Film Festival of Troia [Portugal], 1998 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Jerusalem Film Festival, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Lincoln Center: Graduate Filmmakers King Awards, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - "Lodz Seven" [Warszawski Festiwal Filmowy, Poland], 1993 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Mill Valley Film Festival, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Nantucket Film Festival, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - "Over Yonder (Jonathan's Song)" [New York Film Festival], 2001 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Stockholm Film Festival, November 1991 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - "Subway Riders" [London Film Festival], 1981 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Sundance Film Festival, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Tampere International Short Film Festival, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - 10th Annual Independent Feature Film Market Buyer Directory, October 1988 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Tribeca Film Center, Inc., undated (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Danube Film Festival], 1995 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Deauville Festival, France], 1991 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Festival dei Popoli, Italy], 1991 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Festival of Festivals, Toronto], 1985, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Film Festival Rotterdam, Netherlands], 1992, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Hong Kong International Film Festival], 1992 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - "Triple Bogey" [London Film Festival], 1991 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Melbourne International Film Festival, Australia], 1991 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Midnight Sun Film Festival], 1992 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Mostra Internationale del Nuovo Cinema, Pesaro], 1991 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - "Triple Bogey" [New York Film Festival], 1991 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Philafilm / International Philadelphia Film Festival], 1992 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Rennes Film Festival], 1992 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Reykjavik Film Festival, Iceland], 1991 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Rimini Cinema Mostra Internazionale, Italy], 1991 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Semana Internacional De Cine Valladolid, Spain], October 1991 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Sydney Film Festival], 1992 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Taormina Film Festival, Italy], 1992 (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Telluride Film Festival], 1991 (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Tokyo International Film Festival], 1991 (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Uppsala Film Festival, Sweden], 1990 - 1991 (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Vancouver International Film Festival], 1999 (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Venice Film Festival], 1992 (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Wellington Film Festival], 1991 - 1992 (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - "Triple Bogey" [Wine Country Film Festival], 1992 (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - Undergraduate First Run [New York Unversity], 2001 (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - "Unmade Beds" [Viennale, Austria], 1982 (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - Worldfest [Houston, TX], 1992 (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - X Centric [Barcelona, Spain], 2004 (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - Series II, Subseries E: Project Correspondence
    - "Alphabet City", c1983 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - "Alphaville / Alphabet City" [Jean-Luc Godard], 1978 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - "The Blank Generation," "Triple Bogey" [Media Space, Inc.], 1991 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - "Dead Weekend", various (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - "Enter the Masters", 1992 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - "Hard On Berlin", 1991, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - "Joey Breaker", 1993 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - "Just An American Boy", 2001 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - "Kid Killer", 1993 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - "La Pacifica", 1999 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - "Love at 30", 1985 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - "Mrs. Dogg", various (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - "Pronto!", 2005 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - "Sacher Torte", 1984 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - "Short Lives / Death Valley '89", 1986 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - "The Theresa Stern Story", 1989 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - "Triple Bogey", 1992, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - "29 Palms", 2001 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - "Xodus 5", 2000 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Series III: Press
  - Series III, Subseries A: About Amos Poe
    - American Video Awards, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Amos Poe's Autograph [Premiere Issue], May 13, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Amos Poe's Autograph [#2], August 15, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - [Assorted Press about Poe], various (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - "New York Independent Directors" [Esquire Magazine, Japan], November 1991 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - "Who's Who: Amos Poe" by Eddie Cockrell, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Series III, Subseries B: Clips of Interest
    - "A Comeback for Short Films is Linked to the Web" by Marion Hart [New York Times], January 14, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - "A French Girl, a Chinese Lover and Colonial Days in Old Vietnam" by Vincent Canby [New York Times], October 30, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - "Annals of Warfare: the Bioweaponeers" by Richard Preston [The New Yorker], 1998 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - "A Reporter at Large: Chinatown - I" [The New Yorker], 1991 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - "A Sling Blade Producer Tells All" by Warren St. John [New York Observer], March 24, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - "A Woman in the Summer" by Roger Rosenblatt, undated (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - "Books of The Times" by Christopher Lehmann - Haupt [New York Times], undated (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - [Bryan Hunt Interview], 1981 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - "The Cantor and the Klansman" by Daniel S. Levy [TIME Magazine], February 17, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - "Daisy Hall: They Don't Come Fresher" by Graham Fuller [Interview Magazine], July 1991 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - "Film or Digital? Don't Fight. Coexist." by John Bailey [New York Times], February 18, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - "Follow the Muse: Inspiration to Balance Lofty and Light" by Rick Lyman [New York Times], February 16, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - "Her Horses Got Wings, They Can Fly" by Dave Marsh [Rolling Stone], 1976 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - "The Jews of Hollywood" by Hannah Brown [The Jerusalem Post Magazine], February 7, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - "Letter From Japan: The Auteur of Anime, A Visit With the Elusive Genius Hayao Miyazaki" by Margaret Talbot [The New Yorker], January 17, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - [Lew Wasserman Obituaries], 2002 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - ["Murdoch / Kane," Wall St. Journal], November 1, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - "The Music of Hate Rocks in Germany" by Ferdinand Protzman [New York Times], December 2, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - [New York Post Headline Clips], 1980 (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - "On Writing" [Writers Guild of America East, Volumes 3 and 12], March 1995, June 2001 (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - "The Poe File" [Assorted Clips of Interest], various (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - [Services and Production Periodicals], various (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - ["San Francisco 1906" Coverage], 1989 (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - "Truly Orson" by Geoff Andrew [Time Out Magazine], February 17 - 24, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 49)
- Series IV: Teaching Materials
  - Series IV, Subseries A: Course Components
    - "Advanced Production Workshop" [New York University], 2003 - 2004 (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - Buffalo Niagara Convention and Visitors Bureau, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - "Editing Workshop" [Melody, London], Spring 2000 (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - "Fundamentals of Pos/t Production", 1999 (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - [Miscellaneous: New York University and State University of New York at Buffalo], 2005 (Box 27, Folder 54)
    - New York University: Florence, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 55)
    - New York University: Florence, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 56)
    - New York University, Tisch School of the Arts [Agreements], various (Box 27, Folder 57)
    - School of Visual Arts [Bulletin], Fall 1996 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo: "Hollywood Comes to Buffalo", 1998 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - [State University of New York at Buffalo Miscellaneous], 2004 - 2005 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo: Narrative Filmmaking, Screenwriting II, 2004, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo: Screenwriting, 2004 - 2005 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Series IV, Subseries B: Miscellaneous Reading
    - "Film Has Nothing to do With Literature" by Ingmar Bergman, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - "Producing and Directing the Short Film and Video" by Peter W. Rea and David K. Irving [2nd Edition with Notes], 2001 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - "Recycled Culture in Contemporary Art and Film: The Uses of Nostalgia" by Vera Dika, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - "Shapeshifter," "The Writer's Journey", undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - "16mm" [Handouts], undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - "The Subtext of Meaning", undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Series V: Correspondence
  - Series V, Subseries A: Professional
    - Baldwin, Stephen, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Cervi, Marina and Chiesa, Adriana, 1987 - 1988 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Coltrane, Robbie, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Fineline Features, New Line Cinema, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Ford, Francis Ford, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Greines, Emily, 2001 - 2002 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Josephson, Barry [Columbia Pictures], 1993 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Lubin, Mike [The Gersh Agency], 2003 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Mainline Pictures, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Meridian Entertainment Corp., 1992 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Mitchell, Eric, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - National Academy of Video Arts and Sciences, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - New Alphaville Productions, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Picker, David [Columbia Pictures], 1987 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - The Pioneer Theater, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Prassis, Tom [Original Cinema], 1995 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Ragsdale, Tina [Hudson Media], 1991 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Roos, Fred, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Rowe, Jill, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Starr, Steven, 1986 - 1987 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Techranian, Yalda [Live Entertainment], 1995 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - The Video Store, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - William Morris Agency, various (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Wohlgemuth, Peter, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Woods, Cary, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - World Film Services, various (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Writers Guild of America, East, various (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Series V, Subseries B: Personal
    - Henry, Patrick, 1988 - 1996 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Pasinska, Ania, 1993 - 1994 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Spacey, Kevin, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - [Various Personal Correspondence and Ephemera] (Box 28, Folder 42)
- Series VI: Photography
  - Series VI, Subseries A: Amos Poe Productions
    - "Alphabet City", c1984 (Box 29)
    - "The Blank Generation", undated (Box 29)
    - "The Foreigner", undated (Box 29)
    - "Frogs For Snakes", undated (Box 29)
    - "Gone Fishin' ", undated (Box 29)
    - "John the Cop" [Slides], c1996 (Binder 71)
    - "Native Intelligence of the Rebel Breed", 1978 (Box 29)
    - [NYU Crew Polaroids], 2001 (Binder 71)
    - [Production Polaroids], 1988 - 1989 (Binder 71)
    - "Rocket Gibraltar" [with Art Forum Correspondence], 1987 (Box 29)
    - "Subway Riders", undated (Box 30)
    - "Triple Bogey", undated (Box 30)
    - "Unmade Beds", undated (Box 30)
  - Series VI, Subseries B: Other Productions
    - "Dark Obsession" by Nick Broomfield, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - "Pink Flamingos" by John Waters, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - "Reefer Madness," "Sex Madness", c1973 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - "Variety" by Bette Gordon, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Series VI, Subseries C: Talent Files
    - Agentur Sanna Hubchen, "New Faces" [Catalog], undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Amos Poe by Gabor Szitanyi, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - [Amos Poe, Stichting Film Festival Rotterdam], 1992 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Elizabeth Valgiusti: "Dead at Last" Profile by Amos Poe, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - "The Ford Book", Summer / Fall 1983 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      The white paper elements indicate talent of interest. Please do not remove.
    - "Fotoliste 1982" [Catalog with Notes] (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Iggy Pop, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - "Momo File" [With Correspondence], 1994 - 1995 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - "Nathalie File", undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - [Various Talent File], undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - "Wilhelmina Women" [Catalog], Spring / Summer 1983 (Box 31, Folder 15)
      The white paper elements in this catalog indicate talent of interest. Please do not remove.
    - [Various Talent #1], undated (Box 32)
    - [Various Talent #2], undated (Box 33)
  - Series VI, Subseries D: Personal
    - "A Beach Behind Harbor View Hotel" [Sullivan St., NYC], undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - "Amos, Barbara, John I, Bakersfield, Vt.", September 1972 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - [B + W Portraits, Etc.], undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - "Bates '78", 1978 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Charlesworth, Sarah, various (Box 31, Folder 20)
      These photographic elements were removed from the Sarah Charlesworth Series I Subject File.